http://www.fysa.com/service/privacy/

Skip to Main Content
Main
AdvertisingCOVID-19RefereesState TournamentsRisk Management & SafeSportSponsors
The site navigation utilizes arrow, enter, escape, and space bar key commands. Left and right arrows move across top level links and expand / close menus in sub levels. Up and Down arrows will open main level menus and toggle through sub tier links. Enter and space open menus and escape closes them as well. Tab will move on to the next part of the site rather than go through menu items.
Menu
About
Who We Are
Who We Are
Board of Directors
Board of Directors
Directory
Upcoming Meetings
ODP
What is ODP?
What is ODP?
ODP FAQs
ODP FAQs
ODP Tryouts
ODP Tryouts
ODP Selections
ODP Selections
Resources
Concussion Awareness
Recreational
What is Recreational Soccer?
What is Recreational Soccer?
How to Start a New Program
How to Start a New Program
FYSA Recreational Committee
FYSA Recreational Committee
Coaching Resources
Coaching Resources
Parent Resources
Parent Resources
Player Resources
Player Resources
FYSA Bucks Store
FYSA Bucks Store
TOPSoccer
TOPSoccer "Soccer Special Needs"
TOPSoccer "Soccer Special Needs"
TOPSoccer Committee
TOPSoccer Committee
TOPSoccer Program Finder
TOPSoccer Program Finder
TOPSoccer Program Resources
TOPSoccer Program Resources
Privacy Policy
At the Florida Youth Soccer Association (FYSA) our goal is to provide a fun, informative and safe interactive online experience for all of the children and parents who make up the FYSA family. We want you to understand and feel comfortable with this site’s process of gathering information from users, and we want you to know exactly how that information is used and what your rights are with regards to all of the information collected.
This Privacy Statement is intended to educate parents and youngsters about the steps they can take to safeguard their privacy when visiting fysa.com or any of the other exciting websites that have links to and from the Florida Youth Soccer Association. We also hope that the information presented here demonstrates our total commitment to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”). In doing so, the following discloses our information collection and dissemination practices for this website: fysa.com.
If you have any concern that FYSA is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should e-mail FYSA at info@fysa.com, or use the contact information below:
Florida Youth Soccer Association
2828 Lake Myrtle Park Road
Auburndale, FL 33823
Phone: 863.268.8220
Personal Identification Information
We may request personal identification information from you (such as your last name, age, city and state) in connection with activities, services or resources we make available on any of our sites. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, we reasonably endeavor to ensure that we never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user to any third party without having received your permission (through opt-in or similar procedures) except as provided for herein or otherwise as permitted or required under law.
If you do provide us with personal information for any of these activities, we may use it to conduct the activity.
In certain circumstances, the Florida Youth Soccer Association may share personal identification information with trusted service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services or we may share this aggregate statistical information with other third parties, or ensure the confidentiality and security of this information, service providers must agree to safeguard all information in strict compliance with our policy. We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We collect non-personal identification information through the use of, without limitation, the following types of methodology:
"Cookie" technology: A "cookie" is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system.
"IP address tracking": An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our sites, our servers log your IP address.
"Web beacons": A Web beacon, or "clear gif," is a small graphic image on a webpage or web-based document that a website can use to determine information about a user.
Non-personal identification information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, technical information about your means of connection to our sites—such as the operating systems and the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information. Our systems may also automatically gather information about the areas you visit and search terms you utilize on our sites and about the links you may select from within our sites to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online.
We use such information for our business purposes, and, in particular, primarily to administer the sites, and, in the aggregate, to what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FYSA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Newsletters
If a user wishes to subscribe to our Newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. All newsletters sent out through FYSA are appropriate for all ages.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. This website takes every precaution to protect our user’s information. We do not ask our users for sensitive information and all our information is protected both online and off-line. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to the Director of Communications at communications@fysa.com.
User Submissions
This site provides users with an opportunity to submit their own articles and comments on soccer. All user submissions are edited by our staff for appropriate language and content. Full names and contact information from the submissions are not used on the site unless permission is granted from the submitter.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. To opt-out, you can simply send an email Director of Communications at communications@fysa.com.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the option for changing and modifying information previously provided. Email the changes to info@fysa.com.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact Jared White at Florida Youth Soccer Association, 2828 Lake Myrtle Park Road, Auburndale, FL 33823 or email communications@fysa.com.
LEGAL STATEMENT
All content and images on www.fysa.com are owned by Florida Youth Soccer Association unless credited to a partner. Any reuse of the content and images is forbidden without consent from Florida Youth Soccer Association.
Close
